[
	{
		"question": "In 2003, Morocco made the highly unusual offer to send 2,000 _____ to assist the United States' war efforts in Iraq.?",
		"options": [
			"Girl scouts",
			"Trained chefs",
			"Diapers"
		],
		"answer": "Monkeys"
	},
	{
		"question": "While president of the United States, John Adams had a dog named Juno and a dog named _____.?",
		"options": [
			"Bruno",
			"Jesus",
			"Santa"
		],
		"answer": "Satan"
	},
	{
		"question": "The inventor of the laxative Ex-Lax has the unusual name Max _____.?",
		"options": [
			"Size",
			"Power",
			"Lad"
		],
		"answer": "Kiss"
	},
	{
		"question": "Ben and Jerry only started making ice cream because it was too expensive to make _____.?",
		"options": [
			"Airplanes",
			"Condoms",
			"Cheesecake"
		],
		"answer": "Bagels"
	},
	{
		"question": "Huggies Brazil developed a phone app that tells you when a baby's diaper is wet. It's called _____.?",
		"options": [
			"placeholder1",
			"placeholder2",
			"placeholder3"
		],
		"answer": "Tweetpee"
	},
	{
		"question": "In 1976 boxing legend Muhammad Ali released an education children's album titled 'Ali and His Gang Vs. Mr. _____.'?",
		"options": [
			"placeholder1",
			"placeholder2",
			"placeholder3"
		],
		"answer": "Tooth Decay"
	},
	{
		"question": "During a famous fire in 1567, a Norwegian man named Hans Steininger died after tripping over a _____.?",
		"options": [
			"placeholder1",
			"placeholder2",
			"placeholder3"
		],
		"answer": "Beard"
	},
	{
		"question": "The sound of E.T. walking was made by someone squishing _____.?",
		"options": [
			"placeholder1",
			"placeholder2",
			"placeholder3"
		],
		"answer": "Jell-o"
	},
	{
		"question": "In the video game, The Sims, they speak _____.",
		"options": [
			"placeholder1",
			"placeholder2",
			"placeholder3"
		],
		"answer": "Simlish"
	},
	{
		"question": "Marcella Hazan is the culinary guru who pioneered the unusual technique of cooking duck with a _____.?",
		"options": [
			"placeholder1",
			"placeholder2",
			"placeholder3"
		],
		"answer": "Hair dryer"
	},
	{
		"question": "A woman in Muncie, Indiana was hospitalized after trying to remove a callus on her foot with a _____.?",
		"options": [
			"placeholder1",
			"placeholder2",
			"placeholder3"
		],
		"answer": "Shotgun"
	},
	{
		"question": "A study published in the journal Anthrozoo reported that cows produce 5% more milk when they are given _____.?",
		"options": [
			"150",
			"201",
			"200"
		],
		"answer": "Names"
	}
]